<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>reading on The Blog of Krishan Wyse</title><link>https://kwyse.github.io/categories/reading/</link><description>Recent content in reading on The Blog of Krishan Wyse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kwyse.github.io/categories/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Books of 2019</title><link>https://kwyse.github.io/posts/books-of-2019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kwyse.github.io/posts/books-of-2019/</guid><description>I was a gamer. Was. Words on a page did not enrapture me to the degree that interactive media did. Symbiosis between the visual, aural, narrative, and interactive was beauty itself.
That's not to say I didn't read. Games have their fair share of text, but I had trouble maintaining focus when reading physical books. In fact, the first five Harry Potter books are the only fiction books I can recall reading in my life prior to graduating from university.</description></item><item><title>Book Recommendation: Programming Rust</title><link>https://kwyse.github.io/posts/book-recommendation-programming-rust/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kwyse.github.io/posts/book-recommendation-programming-rust/</guid><description>Most of us can agree that Rust's learning curve is steep. I've been using it for hobby projects for the last few years but I'm still hesitant to use it when I'm constrained by a deadline, because of the upfront cost in development time. And that's frustrating, because I really believe that the benefits it offers outweigh that.
Programming Rust is included in the latest Humble Functional Programming book bundle. Take a look on Amazon and you'll see it's getting some pretty rave reviews.</description></item></channel></rss>