<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>twid on The Blog of Krishan Wyse</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/tags/twid/</link><description>Recent content in twid on The Blog of Krishan Wyse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.kwyse.com/tags/twid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>This Week I Discovered: Vasovagal Syncope</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-vasovagal-syncope/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-vasovagal-syncope/</guid><description>I sprained my ankle during the week before last. Walking was painful for the subsequent few days but it was manageable. The pain was moderate but tolerable. Then this past Tuesday I fainted! And it's related.
The medical professionals tell me that I'm completely healthy, and what happened to me is a case of vasovagal syncope. Vasovagal syncope is fainting because of your body overreacting to certain triggers. One of these triggers is pain, and it needn't even be severe pain!</description></item><item><title>This Week I Discovered: CliftonStrengths</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-clifton-strenths/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-clifton-strenths/</guid><description>I came across this talk by Scott Dinsmore. It's geared towards those who feel trapped trapped in their current circumstances, yet my main take-away was his recommendation on StrengthsFinder 2.0, now called CliftonStrengths. I took the plunge and bought it since this isn't the first time it's been recommended.
The book itself is only half of what you're getting as the back sleeve includes a code you can use to take the online assessment.</description></item><item><title>This Week I Discovered: Tmux</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-tmux/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-tmux/</guid><description>Tmux seems like a natural progression from last week's Vim Minimalism, right? It's associated with the typical Vim power user setup. I remember playing with it back when I first started using Vim as well. The problem I had was why. Vim already has panes, what many other applications would call split windows. And if you use a tiling window manager like i3, you have panes at the application level as well.</description></item><item><title>This Week I Discovered: Vim Minimalism</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-vim-minimalism/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-vim-minimalism/</guid><description>Last month marked four years since I started my dotfiles repository on GitHub. Now it's in a state of disrepair! I had no idea that I hadn't made a single commit to it throughout 2017. I did though, I just didn't push them. There are local changes on every computer that I work with. Some were the results of experiments I later forgot about and others were quickly-needed hacks that I didn't find time to refactor and stabilise.</description></item><item><title>This Week I Discovered: RSS</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-rss/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-rss/</guid><description>This is actually a rediscovery. A colleague was telling me about Feedly back in 2013 when I was scrambling around in my first job. I had narrower interests that were sufficiently sated with GameTrailers.com and other video-heavy publications. Times have changed! My interests are broader. Commutes (often without Internet access) are the best times to peruse news. I want to give priority to news targeted at my interests rather than news discovery.</description></item><item><title>This Week I Discovered: OpenMW</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-open-mw/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-open-mw/</guid><description>Two weeks back I installed Gentoo with the intention to use it as my primary desktop. Naturally I need games to play. My go-to benchmark for the state of Linux gaming has always been the Wine Application Database, so I checked it for a game I knew I could sink countless hours into.
Well it turns out the results for Oblivion are not too promising, especially for Steam. Maybe Morrowind fairs better?</description></item></channel></rss>