<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blogging on The Blog of Krishan Wyse</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/tags/blogging/</link><description>Recent content in blogging on The Blog of Krishan Wyse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.kwyse.com/tags/blogging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploying an ox-hugo blog with GitHub Actions</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/deploying-ox-hugo-blog-with-github-actions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/deploying-ox-hugo-blog-with-github-actions/</guid><description>The blogging flow provided by ox-hugo suggests that Markdown files should be committed to the source repository along with the Org file. I'm reluctant to do that because the Markdown files are effectively a build artefact in this flow. I also couldn't find any information on how to integrate ox-hugo's export functionality with a continuous integration service.
Fortunately, it's quite simple to do with GitHub Actions. After following the instructions for the hugo-setup Action (these at the time of writing), we must then export the Org file as part of the workflow.</description></item><item><title>Hugo, Two Weeks In</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/hugo-two-weeks-in/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/hugo-two-weeks-in/</guid><description>My last post about Hugo focused on getting it set up. It finished with a few ideas on improvements. Maybe you've noticed a few implemented since then =]
One-liner improvements Some of these were very simple to add. The theme I'm using, Minimo, supports adding a reading time to posts with one addition to config.toml.
showReadingTime = true It's a small addition yet adds noted value for the reader.
The next change instead provides insight for the sight maintainer:</description></item><item><title>This Week I Discovered: RSS</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-rss/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/twid-rss/</guid><description>This is actually a rediscovery. A colleague was telling me about Feedly back in 2013 when I was scrambling around in my first job. I had narrower interests that were sufficiently sated with GameTrailers.com and other video-heavy publications. Times have changed! My interests are broader. Commutes (often without Internet access) are the best times to peruse news. I want to give priority to news targeted at my interests rather than news discovery.</description></item><item><title>Hail, Hugo!</title><link>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/hail-hugo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kwyse.com/posts/hail-hugo/</guid><description>One of my goals this holiday season was to relaunch my blog. My previous attempt failed because there was too much friction in actually blogging. It was an Iron-backed Rust web app using PostgreSQL and Diesel on a DigitalOcean host behind NGINX. It was my first time using most of these technologies for anything serious. I learnt a lot about them in the course of building that blog but the fifth blog post never saw the light of day.</description></item></channel></rss>